http://hidesertcomputers.com/privacy-statement

HomeServicesContact UsBlogCOVID-19 AssistanceMoreHomeServicesContact UsBlogCOVID-19 AssistanceHomeServicesContact UsBlogCOVID-19 Assistance
Privacy Statement We at Hi-Desert Computers respect your online time and privacy. Below, we'll describe the privacy practices for this website.Personal Information At hidesertcomputers.com and hdcca.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit hidesertcomputers.com on the web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, email address, telephone number or address in order to respond to your enquiry and/or feedback. We do not collect any personal information without your consent. Hi-Desert Computers does not share information about individual users with any third party.If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need -- to correspond with you over your enquiry and/or feedback, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics to help us serve our visitors and customers better.Business Relationshipshidesertcomputers.com may contain links to other websites. Hi-Desert Computers is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websitesCookiesThere is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Cookies are only used at the interactive portion of the website.
Copyright © 2020 Hi Desert Computers - All Rights Reserved.Privacy StatementTerms of Service
